{
  "version": 2.0,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT an Electronic array Geometry?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Wenner Array",
        "b": "Pole- Dipole Array",
        "c": "Dipole-Wenner Array",
        "d": "Schlumberger Array"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "The unit of percolation rate of the soil is __________.",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Unitless",
        "b": "g/cc",
        "c": "ml/s",
        "d": "cm/s"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "Which IS code is used in this experiment?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "IS 1199:1959",
        "b": "IS 15736:2007",
        "c": "IS 800:2007",
        "d": "IS 15658:2006"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "The ground resistivity calculated from measured resistance and a geometric factor derived for the condition where the ground is homogeneous and isotropic is",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Resistivity",
        "b": "True Resistivity",
        "c": "Resistivity imaging",
        "d": "Apparent Resistivity"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "d",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "Which type of rock has the highest resistivity?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Igneous rocks",
        "b": "Sedimentary rocks",
        "c": "Metamorphic rocks",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "Which type of rocks has the lowest resistivity?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Igneous rocks",
        "b": "Sedimentary rocks",
        "c": "Metamorphic rocks",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "In the Schlumberger array, the electrodes are placed at equal distances?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "True",
        "b": "False"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "Ohm's law states that the current through a conductor between two points is inversely proportional to the voltage across the two points.",
      "answers": {
        "a": "True",
        "b": "False"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "The positive terminal of the battery is known as",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Anode",
        "b": "Cathode",
        "c": "Electrode",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "The negative terminal of the battery is known as",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Anode",
        "b": "Cathode",
        "c": "Electrode",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": ""
    }
  ]
}
